<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<data>
	<pages>
		<page id="1" name="story" type="articles">
			<arts>
				<art id="1">
					<title>What is a Headstone ?</title>
					<link>memorials/story/what-is-a-headstone-1</link>
					<description>For many people buying a memorial can be a daunting prospect, especially if it is the first time they have been involved in the process. Few people are aware that headstones and memorial plaques can be purchased from a variety of sources.<![CDATA[ <br/><br/>To find out more please call Forever Shining at 1300 851 181 | Mobile 0419 945 950 or use <a target="_default" href="http://www.forevershining.com.au/contact/">Contact Page</a>.<br/> You can also read more in our online <a target="_blank" href="http://www.forevershining.com.au/design-3d/catalog.html">Catalogue</a>]]></description>
					<image>boot/img/Headstone.webp</image>
					<content>Headstone is typically a slab placed upright at the head of a grave. The basic message includes the name, date of birth and death, and a brief message regarding the deceased. Discover the wide range of headstones available at Forever Shining.</content>
				</art>
				<art id="2">
					<title>Step by step to buying ...</title>
					<link>memorials/story/step-by-step-buying-headstone-2</link>
					<description>Our aim is to assist you in the planning of a personal ceremony and to help you in making your loved one’s story beautiful. We strive to assure you that the grave marker you create will be the most fitting tribute to represent your loved one. <![CDATA[<a target="_blank" href="http://www.forevershining.com.au/design-3d/catalog.html"><strong>Read More</strong></a>]]></description>
					<image>boot/img/Cemetery.webp</image>
					<content>Our aim is to assist you in the planning of a personal ceremony and to help you in making your loved one’s story beautiful. We strive to assure you that the grave marker you create will be the most fitting tribute to represent and symbolize your loved one.</content>
				</art>
				<art id="3">
					<title>Amazing laser technology</title>
					<link>memorials/story/amazing-laser-technology-headstones-3</link>
					<description>Amazing laser technology has finally caught up with the cemeteries industry. Laser etching makes it easy to engrave photo realistic portraits into stone. You can even design your own laser etched granite gravestone. <![CDATA[<a target="_blank" href="http://www.forevershining.com.au/design-3d/catalog.html"><strong>Read More</strong></a>]]></description>
					<image>boot/img/Photo.webp</image>
					<content>Amazing laser technology has finally caught up with the cemeteries industry. Laser etching makes it easy to engrave photo realistic portraits into stone. You can even design your own laser etched granite gravestone.</content>
				</art>
				<art id="4">
					<title>Best experience on a PC</title>
					<link>memorials/story/best-experience-on-a-pc-4</link>
					<description>For the best experience please use a PC. You will be able to see a real time 3D visualization. You will be also able to Save Design, send Design to friends and family or download as PDF or share on Facebook. <![CDATA[<a target="_blank" href="http://www.forevershining.com.au/design-3d/catalog.html"><strong>Read More</strong></a>]]></description>
					<image>boot/img/Computer.webp</image>
					<content>Best experience on a PC with Adobe Flash Player. You will be able to see a real time 3D visualization.</content>
				</art>
			</arts>
		</page>	
		<page id="2" name="description" type="products">
			<products>
				<product id="3">
					<name>Traditional Engraved Headstone</name>
					<link>memorials/description/traditional-engraved-headstone-3</link>
					<type>headstone</type>
					<description>Our traditional inscription granite or sandstone headstones have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. These headstones are available in many different granite colours as well as sandstone, together with 9 different colours of inscription and artwork motif to choose from. A polished granite/sandstone headstone will not oxidize or readily deteriorate thereby maintaining good looks for many years.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_3.webp</image>
					<stone>8</stone>
					<formula>Engraved</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="4">
					<name>Laser Etched Black Granite Headstone</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-headstone-4</link>
					<type>headstone</type>
					<description>Our laser-etched black granite headstones have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. The laser etching process allows us to etch beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs, logos and photos into the surface of the granite. This style of headstone is available in a range of shapes and sizes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_4.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="5">
					<name>Bronze Casted and Painted Plaque</name>
					<link>memorials/description/bronze-plaque-5</link>
					<type>plaque</type>
					<description>Bronze plaques are a recent addition to our range of funerary products to satisfy those customers who prefer a traditional material. Our bronze plaques are cast and painted, and then the top surface of the inscription, motifs and border is machined to highlight the natural bronze colour. The background is painted with a high quality paint of a colour selected by our customer. When the manufacturing operation is complete, the whole plaque is sealed with a high quality clear lacquer that helps to preserve the bright shiny colour of the natural bronze.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_5.webp</image>
					<stone>1</stone>
					<formula>Bronze</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="8">
					<name>Laser Etched Pet Mini Headstone</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-pet-mini-headstone-8</link>
					<type>mini-headstone</type>
					<description>Our laser-etched black granite pet mini headstones have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. The laser etching process allows us to etch beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs, logos and photos into the surface of the granite. This style of headstone is available in a range of shapes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_8.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>				
				<product id="9">
					<name>Laser Etched Black Granite Pet Headstone</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-pet-headstone-9</link>
					<type>headstone</type>
					<description>Our laser-etched black granite pet headstones have been designed to compliment our range of pet memorials. and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. The laser etching process allows us to etch beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs, logos and photos into the surface of the granite. This style of headstone is available in a range of shapes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_9.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>			
				<product id="10">
					<name>Laser Etched Black Granite Pet Plaque</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-pet-plaque-10</link>
					<type>plaque</type>
					<description>Our laser-etched black granite pet plaques have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. The laser etching process allows us to etch beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs, logos and photos into the surface of the granite. This style of plaque is available in a range of rectangular shapes and sizes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_10.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>	
				<product id="11">
					<name>Stainless Steel Vitreous Enamel Pet Urn</name>
					<link>memorials/description/stainless-steel-pet-urn-11</link>
					<type>urn</type>
					<description>A beautiful, unique porcelain inlaid stainless steel urn will be a permanent memorial for family and friends to remember and celebrate the life of a loved one. Our urns can be individualized and personalized to reflect the true nature and personality of the deceased. The porcelain printing process allows us to affix beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs and photos, in full natural colour, onto the porcelain surface. This style of urn is available in a range of shapes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_11.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Enamel</formula>
				</product>	
				<product id="22">
					<name>Laser Etched Black Granite Mini Headstone</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-mini-headstone-22</link>
					<type>mini-headstone</type>
					<description>Our laser-etched black granite mini headstones have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. The laser etching process allows us to etch beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs, logos and photos into the surface of the granite. This style of headstone is available in a range of shapes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_22.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="30">
					<name>Laser Etched Black Granite Plaque</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-plaque-30</link>
					<type>plaque</type>
					<description>Our black granite plaques complement our funeral products and are fancied by customers who prefer using traditional materials for their monument. We laser etch beautiful images, logos and motifs on the plaque’s granite surface, which is available in various rectangular shapes and sizes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_30.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="50">
					<name>Stainless Steel Vitreous Enamel Urn</name>
					<link>memorials/description/stainless-steel-urn-50</link>
					<type>urn</type>
					<description>A beautiful, unique porcelain inlaid stainless steel urn will be a permanent memorial for family and friends to remember and celebrate the life of a loved one. Our urns can be individualized and personalized to reflect the true nature and personality of the deceased. The porcelain printing process allows us to affix beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs and photos, in full natural colour, onto the porcelain surface. This style of urn is available in a range of shapes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_50.webp</image>
					<stone>1</stone>
					<formula>Enamel</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="124">
					<name>Traditional Engraved Monument</name>
					<link>memorials/description/traditional-engraved-monument-124</link>
					<type>monument</type>
					<description>Our traditional inscription granite or sandstone full monuments have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. These monuments are available in many different granite colours as well as sandstone, together with 9 different colours of inscription and artwork motif to choose from. A polished granite/sandstone headstone will not oxidize or readily deteriorate thereby maintaining good looks for many years.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_124.webp</image>
					<stone>8</stone>
					<formula>Engraved</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="125">
					<name>Laser Etched Black Granite Monument</name>
					<link>memorials/description/laser-etched-monument-125</link>
					<type>monument</type>
					<description>Our laser-etched black granite full monuments have been designed to compliment our range of funerary products and satisfy the needs of those customers who wish to continue to use a traditional material for their memorial. The laser etching process allows us to etch beautiful, complex and intricate images of motifs, logos and photos into the surface of the granite. This style of monument is available in a range of shapes and sizes.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_125.webp</image>
					<stone>17</stone>
					<formula>Laser</formula>
				</product>
				<product id="999">
					<name>Bronze Casted and Painted Plaque</name>
					<link>memorials/description/bronze-plaque-5</link>
					<type>plaque</type>
					<description>Bronze plaques are a recent addition to our range of funerary products to satisfy those customers who prefer a traditional material. Our bronze plaques are cast and painted, and then the top surface of the inscription, motifs and border is machined to highlight the natural bronze colour. The background is painted with a high quality paint of a colour selected by our customer. When the manufacturing operation is complete, the whole plaque is sealed with a high quality clear lacquer that helps to preserve the bright shiny colour of the natural bronze.</description>
					<image>boot/img/APP_ID_5.webp</image>
					<stone>1</stone>
					<formula>Bronze</formula>
				</product>
			</products>
		</page>
	</pages>
</data>